http://www.jrjunction.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Jr Junction Train & Hobby
Skip to content
Call Us Today! (315) 451-6551
My Account Remember MeRegisterCart
Search for:
TrainsO Scale Model Trains & ProductsHO Scale Model Trains
& ProductsN Scale Model Trains & ProductsS Scale Model Trains & ProductsG Scale Model Trains & ProductsStandard Scale Model Trains & ProductsModelsPlastic Model Cars & TrucksPlastic Model AirplanesPlastic Models – Military & ArmorPlastic Model Kits – Ships & BoatsPlastic Model Kits – Science FictionRocketsRadio ControlTools & SuppliesScratch Building Tools & SuppliesPaints & GluesContact UsFAQ
Search for:
Privacy PolicyJesse2020-07-14T10:05:03-04:00
Jr Junction Train & Hobby Privacy Policy
Jr Junction Train & Hobby is a firm believer in the protection of its online customers’ privacy. We have implemented a number of procedures and policies which are designed to protect your personal information while using our online services.
Our site uses an online ordering system for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor’s contact information (like their names, address, telephone number, and e-mail address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. If you choose a third-party billing option, financial and personal information will be provided to the billing company. Regardless of if you pay online or by mail in payment, we do not retain your financial information on any of our computers after the approval process.
If the customer has agreed to receive delivery update e-mails, we may submit the e-mail address to the shipping company so the customer can be notified of the shipping status of the package. Currently, we use FedEx for shipping.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Web site, and to provide security. Our site uses “cookies” to keep track of your shopping cart contents.
Whenever sensitive personal or financial information is transmitted, it is sent via a secured connection directly to our main computer using secure sockets layer (SSL) technology. This is the most successfully used method of ensuring private, secure transmission of personal information over the Internet.
Email addresses are collected only for the purpose of contacting you in the future. We WILL NOT sell or rent your e-mail address to other companies or individuals.
We do not collect personal information for children under the age of 13.
We do occasionally share portions of our customer postal mailing list with trusted and approved high-quality companies for shipping your order to you.
In some cases products are drop-shipped directly from the manufacturer. We share only the information the manufacturer needs to fulfill the order and contact the customer.
We may be forced to share customer purchase data to government organizations when compelled by law to do so.
This site gives users the following options to not receive future communications.
If you wish to change your e-mail subscription enter you can do so in your ‘My Account’ settings.
You can send mail to the following postal address:
Jr Junction Train & Hobby, 2716 Erie Blvd East, Syracuse, NY, 13224
You can call the following telephone number: 315-451-6551.
To protect our customers’ accounts we do not accept third-party requests to modify customers’ privacy preferences.
Jr Junction Train & Hobby respects its customers’ privacy and works diligently to protect it.
Material changes to Jr Junction Train & Hobby’ privacy policies will be posted in this Privacy Statement.
This Privacy Statement became effective on 10/01/2011.
Copyright 2020 Jr Junction Train & Hobby - Syracuse, New York
FacebookYouTube
Go to Top
